{
    "subject": "resource/French_colonial_empire",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/French_franc",
    "human_readable": "The currency of French colonial empire is French franc.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9077008366584778,
            "question": "Could people in the French colonies exchange their local currency for a French franc?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8773337006568909,
            "question": "Was the French franc used in the French colonial empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8292829394340515,
            "question": "What currency was used in the French colonial empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7974495887756348,
            "question": "What was the name of the currency used by the French colonial empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.761276364326477,
            "question": "What currency circulated within the territories of the French colonial empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5693552494049072,
            "question": "To what country's monetary system did the French colonial empire adhere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5396684408187866,
            "question": "How did the French colonial empire's currency influence trade with other countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.522887110710144,
            "question": "What was the impact of using the French franc on the economies of the colonies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46579858660697937,
            "question": "Did the use of a standardized currency contribute to economic integration within the French colonial empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43825623393058777,
            "question": "Did France use the same currency across all its colonies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of French colonial empire is French franc.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9341_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did the use of a standardized currency contribute to economic integration within the French colonial empire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9341_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the impact of using the French franc on the economies of the colonies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9341_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the French colonial empire's currency influence trade with other countries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9341_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9341_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation result:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the documents, the official currency of the French Empire is indeed the French franc (Sign: \u20a3, Code: FF), but it also mentions the existence of a separate currency called the CFA franc, which was created in 1945 and has its own fixed parity with the metropolitan franc. This suggests that the French colonial empire had at least two official currencies, not just one."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided clearly indicate that the French franc was indeed used as a currency within the French colonial empire, supporting the statement that it served as the currency for the French colonial empire."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The French Empire has two separate CFA francs for different regions of Western and Central Africa, each with its own economy and monetary system, not a single currency called the \"French franc\".",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}